We've got a new update out.
So let's slow down and talk about it.
as always, there's a lot in this update,
so see the full release notes below.
But the big new feature
that we're going to talk about is
you can finally put affect
speed on faders.
So let's take a look at that. Okay.
So let's take a look at this
brand new feature
by making an effect on the Helios tube.
I'll grab my Helios tube.
I'll go offset sell, sell
only to select just the cells,
and then I'll hit record effect.
And I'll call this Chase.
Okay, so if I hit play on this
Helios chase, you'll see.
We get a chase across this Helios tube.
But this is way too slow, and I want to
dynamically speed it up or slow it down.
How do I do that?
Well, I can put speed on a fader,
so I'll go to my fader
page now
and I'll load any of these empty faders.
Let's take this one in the middle and
I'll go to effect and select the effect.
In this case
the chase that I want to slow down.
And then I can come over here
and switch it from master to affect speed.
It's worth it to know if I select master.
That's going to control both the intensity
and the speed together.
You might want this if you just want to
shut off and turn on an effect entirely.
most instances,
I just want to control the effect speed.
I like using inhibitors
to control the intensity.
you'll see here
I can set the max speed percentage.
I found 500% is great. So we'll keep that.
and then the last thing
I'll do before exiting this menu is add
one of our new buttons,
which is the speed 1 to 1 button.
that's going to reset the speed 1 to 1.
So now I'll hit save on the button
and I'll save the menu.
And here's our speed fader.
You can see my chase stopped.
And that's because my faders at zero.
Now if I start bringing my fader up,
you can see the chase starts again.
and if I go all the way to 500%, it
speeds up to the max.
Now you can either change the max
speed percentage
or just make your effect faster.
So if I go back into my effects menu,
I can change the total time to one second.
Now this is going a lot faster.
So I'm going to hit my speed 1 to 1 button
and see where my base speed is.
You can see that feels pretty nice
if I bring the fader all the way down.
It will stop the effect
because the speed is zero.
That's pretty cool Now just add a Midi
fader into the mix, and it's a party. We.
To see everything that's new in 2.4.6.
Check the release notes down below.
We have a lot of fun new features
and fixes like inhibited faders
come in as red.
There's a lot to love
and we have a lot more coming.
So stay tuned and let me know in
the comments what you want to see more of.
I'll see you next time.
Don't put this in the video.
Just my cursor.
Okay, I'll start that over
because I fucked up.
Fuck. Okay. Okay. Don't use that.
Okay.
you can see
I get this chase on my Helios tube.
That's way too bright. Jeez.
Oh, fuck me.
Will slow that down.
Now and just start it here.